♪ nice to see you ♪
♪ how do it ♪
♪ didn't know you really something then ♪
♪ you make me feel like i ♪
♪ don't believe that ♪
♪ it's all up in my heart and all up in my spinal chance ♪
刚刚又去买了盆盆栽
我真的比起鲜花太爱买盆栽了
同样的价格超大一盆鲜花只能买小小一束
而且只能活一段时间
还在多好呀
我突然发现我的铃兰又长出来了
这是我去年5月份买的那盆
然后他到秋天就枯了嘛
我就把枯叶都剪了
没想到1年后它又长出新的芽了
今年5月又有新的幸运铃兰了
好开心
今天是我上法语课以来第一个公共假期复活节
然后破例邀请我罗拉和酱一起去她家过
其实这一个月以来
我们四个人就一直在约
想办法周末见个面具一句这样
但是不是因为罢工啊
就是因为各种原因没有成型过
就毕业之后大家都很忙嘛
就很难聚起来
这次好不容易能再聚一次
我们出发吧
i remember the way
you plan to me
as i remember
i remember me when we got a shooting star
i remember i remember all the things that we share
♪ and the promise we made just you ♪
and i i remember all the left here
we should all the wishes
♪ we made upon ♪
the roof that d
♪ do you remember when we were dancing in the rain ♪
♪ and that december ♪
and i remember when my father
thought you were a bul
i remember all the things to me
this is my house
so it's everyone
this is my sweet studio
remember all the things that we should
♪ and the promise we made just you ♪
♪ and i i remember all the left are we sh all the wishes ♪
♪ we made up on the roof that d ♪
♪ 啊吧吧吧吧吧吧吧吧吧吧吧吧吧吧 ♪
♪ ah ♪
♪ yes ♪
♪ i remember all the things that we shared ♪
♪ and the promise we made just you ♪
♪ and i i remember all the lecture ♪
we shared all the wishes
♪ we made up above the rift that d ♪
so hashi
who cares
it's fri
well
i'm joke不吃
我怕把自己吃吧
这个点很remember the way
you read your books as i remember the way
you take your chance
♪ cause i remember the cake ♪
you love the most design
♪ remember the way ♪
♪ you drink a coffee ♪
♪ i remember that poway ♪
♪ you dance with me ♪
♪ when we were dancing in the rainy december ♪
♪ and the way ♪
♪ you smile at me ♪
♪ as i remember ♪
看我终于收到了什么
我们平方和浦东美术馆合作的周边
其实出了好久了
但是因为转运啊
那些我才收到
一起来看一下这个有印章盲盒
然后迷你印章火漆
还有便签
我们就是提取了展览中的一些
阿波罗的缪斯的一些元素做了一些啊
在创作
我觉得出来效果特别棒
这套盲盒印章我特别期待
因为毕竟也是平方第一次出印章
盲盒这种产品嘛
然后我们就提取了不同的缪斯元素
每个盲盒代表一位缪斯
我来拆两个
看我能拆到谁
代表着英雄史诗的卡利欧佩喜欢
要不要再拆一个
不知道能不能拆到隐藏款
哇哇我抽到了阿波罗那菠萝是隐藏款的
天哪
我说也太准了点吧哈这运气也太好了吧
好开心啊
接下来是火漆印章
这个包装质感特别棒
这里面应该是使用说明
里面有两个火漆的替换头
然后蜡勺蜡粒蜡烛都有哦
这个手柄复古立柱式的
我们当时做了好久
但出来的效果特别棒
还有和迷你小印章
这个大小和刚刚我抽出来的盲盒印章差不多大
但是是长条形的那种
我想做这种长条形一张很久了
就特别可爱
然后又很便携
接下来是两款便签
上面也是两位缪斯的元素组成的纹理
这种便签卡特别好用
无论是日常的书写啊
或者啊
作为礼物中的小卡或者留言卡都可以用等等
就把它放到手帐里
♪ 啊啊啊啊 ♪
啊啊啊啊
♪ one two three thousand of miles away ♪
♪ the sky's dress ♪
♪ this blue ♪
♪ it says ♪
♪ if i'm stuck in yesterday ♪
♪ when i'm thinking of you ♪
♪ because when you have your morning ♪
♪ call ♪
♪ i'm turning out the lights ♪
♪ so i could dream and when you smile through the screen ♪
♪ i wish you could be with me ♪
♪ so i lay my head to wrist ♪
♪ when the sun is rising ♪
♪ i'll start a brand ♪
♪ new day when the moon ♪
♪ it is sharing ♪
♪ i want to be with you in all the places ♪
♪ you have been so today ♪
♪ i am time travelling under all day ♪
i am time traveling
一辆自行车
准备骑到接班里那边
every time that you are closing your eyes
♪ i will be beside you ♪
♪ and my heart with fiat customized fly ♪
♪ right to you ♪
cause when i dive into the traffic
♪ the heck off your phone ♪
♪ loses to like him ♪
♪ i'm martired of your life and so far ♪
♪ but ever suit ♪
♪ so i lay my head to run this time ♪
♪ the sun is rising ♪
♪ i started a new thing around the moon is sh i want to be with you ♪
♪ and all the places you have been so ♪
这朵蒲公英好完整啊
推不掉
推不动了
嗯我去找
嗯好的
♪ so today i am times of li ♪
♪ don't follow fi ♪
♪ don't know something ♪
♪ don't follow the way up fi ♪
♪ don't want to fb ♪
♪ so i lay my head to raise ♪
♪ the sun is rising ♪
♪ i started brand new day when the moon ♪
♪ he is shining ♪
♪ i want to be with you one ♪
♪ and all the places ♪
♪ you have been ♪
没事
那他鸡蛋是这样送进来
然后天气这样送牛奶的
感谢您的宝贝
感谢队长
光是初恋
让我们不在此
就非常经典的法式书
最近我在日常还有旅游的时候又买了一些餐具
就实在没有忍住嗯
大部分都是比较便携的那种
刀叉那些就想着比较好带回国嘛
但是还是有非常心动的玻璃制品
让我们一起看一下吧
先来拆这袋
这是加巴黎的vintage店淘到的
然后他大部分卖的都是衣服
但是我觉得我最近逛店
永远在看这家店的家具啊啊摆设啊
那些
就是这款它比视频中拍出来更暗一点
就是那种深色的茶棕色的感觉
就非常有气质的一个颜色
然后外形很简洁嘛
就非常百搭
当时他放在店里的时候
是标签放在这个杯子里啊
写酒我以为就这个杯子酒
没想到是一套酒
我觉得特别划算
喜欢
还是这个这个是我从瑞典带回来的
就是这款杯子它是一个杯身特别短的高脚杯
然后中间这个有这种手绘感觉的纹理
特别像一颗球
自己在转动
我觉得这个杯子作为啊饮品啊什么喝的话
其实作用挺有限的
但是作为装饰品或者啊放首饰啊
比如戒指放在里面
或者啊项链挂在上面都特别好看
接下来是mac买的东西
其实里面其实有两次购买的东西
然后两次都是陪朋友去max c
但每次出来手里都多了些残疾
这包里面是三把特别可爱的刀叉
先介绍这个
他特别像那个耕地用的啊
锄头铲子就奇奇怪怪的
可可爱的
接下来是对刀叉不规则的嗯
这把是个黄油刀
前面是光滑的
后面是有纹理的
然后特别厚实
手感特别棒
这个是一个像树枝一样的叉子
这一对放在这太可爱了
最后还有一
这一套特别圆润
你有没有觉得特别是它下面这边也是圆圆的
就整个看起来都特别可爱
然后有点像那种儿童餐具
来讲这次开箱的全家福
明明就一张嘴
为什么会有这么多好看的餐具呢
我的铃兰已经完全长开了
长得好好
感觉好幸运
法语好难啊